Did you see the new budget memo
this morning?
(Leonard:)Yeah, more cutbacks.
(Sheldon:)Unacceptable. It baffles me...
(Sheldon:)...why they don't simply let some of you go
so there's money available for my research.
(Leonard:)You know what baffles me, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)Based on your academic record,
any number of things, I would imagine.
LESLIE: Hey, guys.
- Hi, Leslie.
(Leslie:)I got the approval
for the rapid prototyper.
(Howard:)That's great, Leslie. Thanks.
(Leslie:)You scratch my back, I scratch yours.
[GROWLS]
(Raj:)What was all that about?
(Howard:)Oh, uh, no big deal.
(Howard:)They gave Leslie control
over some unrestricted grant money.
(Leonard:)Yeah, okay, but what's with
the back scratching and the meow?
(Sheldon:)I believe the back-scratching metaphor
describes a quid pro quo situation...
...where one party provides services
to the second party...
(Sheldon:)- ...in compensation for a similar action.
- Thank you.
The meow, that sounded to me
like an African civet cat.